https://splashtacular.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy Personal InformationSplashtacular is committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors. Please review the information below to understand how we treat your personal information.We collect, store and use the following kinds of personal information.Information about your computer and about your visits to our site, including your IP address, geographical location, browser type and version, operating system, referral source, length of visit, page views and website navigation pathsInformation that you provide to when completing the contact form including your name, company, industry, email and phone number.Personal Information submitted to us through our website will be used to send you marketing communications relating to our business or to respond to an inquiry you made through our contact form.The Splashtacular website uses cookies, tracking pixels and related technologies. Cookies are small data files that are served by our website and stored on your device. Our site uses cookies dropped by us or third parties for a variety of purposes including to operate and personalize the website. Also, cookies may also be used to track how you use the site to target ads to you on other websites. If you do not wish to see personalized ads, please opt-out or adjust your privacy settings within your internet browser (Google Chrome, Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, Safari). EU Data Regulations & Data Protection ContactIn case of concern, please contact Alex Weidman, sales@splashtacular.com.Your individual privacy is important to us. To that end:What we do with your data: Your data is used to send email and postal messages to you. It may be used to contact you via telephone.How we look after your data: We secure your data using a secure sockets layer (SSL), a standard security technology for establishing an encrypted link between a server and a client—typically a web server (website) and a browser.Why we need your data: Your data is used for normal business transactions in accordance with your request. Additionally, we provide additional marketing and sales messages to you that are based on your prior interest in our products and services. You may always opt out of any contact with us.How long we need it: We keep your information as long as it is reasonable to assume you are still interested in our products and services.What your rights are: At any time, please use our unsubscribe tool and we’ll stop contacting you. You also have the right to erase your personally identifiable information from our system, once it is no longer necessary for the purpose for which it was originally collected. Contact our Data Protection Contact to view your information (this may take up to one month), and object to any individual use of your information. You have the right to change your information at any time, with changes taking place no later than one month.
401 N. East StreetPaola, KS 66071Toll Free: 800.844.5334UK: +00 44 1403 334375China: +86 14714910540Fax: 913.294.2496California Contractors License #1056997Mon - Fri: 08:00 - 05:00
Products and ServicesWaterslidesAquatic Play UnitsSpray FeaturesSplashtacular InnovationsKEEP IT NEW™ Maintenance
Who We ServeContractorsMunicipal CommitteesPrivate Waterparks
Copyright @ 2019 | Made in the USA | Privacy Policy
About Us Who We Are Blog: The Deep EndResourcesProducts & Services Overview Waterslides Aquatic Play Units Spray Features Splashtacular Innovations KEEP IT NEW™ MaintenanceWho We Serve Overview Contractors Municipal Committees Private WaterparksBlogContact Us
Splashtacular, LLCdavid.seooptimizer@gmail.com401 N East St Paola, KS , 66071United Stateshttps://splashtacular.com/https://660216.smushcdn.com/1282826/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/splashtacular-logo-white-1.png?lossy=0&strip=1&webp=1Manufacturer
